dishpromotions.com 2017-04-10

# Privacy Policy | DISH Promotions

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Dish Promotions collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the www.dishpromotions.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Dish Promotions.

 **Personal identification information**  
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users call us, visit our site, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number. We will collect personal identification information from Users **ONLY if they voluntarily submit such information to us**. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities such as placing an order.

 **Non-personal identification information**  
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

 **Web browser cookies**  
Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

 **Protecting Your Privacy**  
Many website tools and plug-ins use cookies to enhance functionality and website user experience. We cannot eliminate all cookies from being stored on your PC from dishpromotions.com. Google does provide an opt out extension for tracking [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

To opt out of dishpromotions.com ID cookie tracking, click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/). _(You must do this on every device you connect to dishpromotions.com from. If you delete your browser history and cookies, you will need to opt out again if visiting dishpromotions.com.)_

 **How we use collected information**  
Dish Promotions may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:  
– To improve customer service  
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.  
– To personalize user experience  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.  
– To improve our Site  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.  
– To process payments  
We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.  
– To send periodic emails  
We may use the email address to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.  
How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

 **Sharing your personal information**  
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

 **Changes to this privacy policy**  
Dish Promotions has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

 **Your acceptance of these terms**  
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

 **Contacting us**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

 **Dish Promotions**  
N56 W13365 Silver Spring Drive  
Menomonee Falls, WI 53051  
1-855-629-3838  
www.dishpromotions.com

This document was last updated on **January 29, 2015**
